<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Battleship++</string>
    <string name="testing">Testing!</string>
    <string name="open_map">Open Map</string>
    <string name="test123">Test123</string>
    <string name="background_water_texture_for_the_string_open_map">background water texture for the @string/open_map</string>
    <string name="app_title">Battleship Reloaded</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tBattleship Reloaded \n\n"

        "Welcome to Battleshships Reloaded\n\n"

        "\t\tEver played Battleships before? Well, this Battleship Reloaded is just as the same as it"
        "sounds. Its \t\tcompletely Reloaded, with its own twists and turns!! So, buckle up for excitement!\n\n"

        "\t\tBattleships Reloaded Game Method: \n\n"
        "\t\tWith the new version of Battleships you can do some of the following stuff: \n\n"

        "\t\tStarting the game, both the players of the game will have a choice of placing their ships on the"
        "gameboard. \t\tEach player will be having 12 points in total in their account and each ships are"
        "worth specific points. You \t\twill be able place any number of ships on the gameboard as long as"
        "the sum of the points of the ships does \t\tnot exceed 12 points. You can always see how many"
        "points are left in the score panel placed in the center \t\tbottom of the screen. To place the ships on "
        "the gameboard screen you simply drag and drop the ships on \t\tthe gameboard panel at whatever"
        "spot you want. You cannot place the ships anywhere beyond the red line \t\tthat will appear on the"
        "Gameboard screen. After you are done placing ships you simply hit the “Done Placing \t\tShips”"
        "button found on the bottom left corner screen below the ship images. The second player will"
        "perform \t\tthe same task and place his ships on the Gameboard grid. The game will start as soon"
        "as the second player \t\twill hit the Done Placing Ships button.\n\n "

        "\tNow it’s time for some fun! Let’s have some! \n\n"

        "\t\tTo play the game further you will have to strategies your game in such a way that the opposite "
        "player will \t\thave a really hard time figuring out where you placed your ships. During the game, "
        "you can perform many \t\ttasks such as moving the ships, rotating the ships, firing on the opponent"
        "ships. The game will go on until one \t\tof the player’s all ships get totally destroyed. To destroy the "
        "ships you will have to guess where the opponent \t\tships might be located. To Fire, you simply "
        "have to click on the ship that you want to use to fire. On pointing \t\tout the ship, you can select the"
        "co-ordinate and then simply hit the fire button. If the opponent has a ship \t\tplaced at the same "
        "coordinate then Congratulations!! You successfully guessed the place for the opponents \t\tship"
        "and you made damage to the ship that is hit. Now player two will have a choice of moving the "
        "coordinate \t\tof the ships, rotate the ships, and also Firing back on the player 1 ships. After you "
        "get done with your turn you \t\tjust hit the “End Turn” button. The game will continue till all of the "
        "ships of the either player gets destroyed.\t\t Sounds fun right? \n\n"

        "\t\tNow Each ship has its own firing and move ability. (Subject to change) \n\n"
        "\t\tMoves: 	(Subject to change) \n"
        "\t\tCruiser: 3 blocks per move\n"
        "\t\tBattleships: 2 blocks per move\n"
        "\t\tDestroyer: 2 blocks per move\n"
        "\t\tAir-Craft Carrier: 1 block per move\n"
        "\t\tSubmarine: 2 blocks per move\n"

    </string>
</resources>
